{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "It will not be long ___ he comes back.",
      "a": "after",
      "b": "before",
      "c": "until",
      "d": "when",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Before: earlier than a particular event or action",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Be careful, ___ you'll make grammatical mistakes.",
      "a": "and",
      "b": "if",
      "c": "or",
      "d": "but",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Or: used between two words or phrases to show that either of two things is possible",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Study hard, ___ you'll make great progress.",
      "a": "and",
      "b": "or",
      "c": "but",
      "d": "while",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- And: used to join two words, phrases etc referring to things that are related in some way",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I don't like running ___ climbing. \"I don't like running, ___ I like climbing very much.\"",
      "a": "and, and",
      "b": "and, but",
      "c": "or, but",
      "d": "or, and",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Or: used between two words or phrases to show that either of two things is possible \n- And: used to say that one action or event follows another",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The day broke, ___ the birds were beginning to sing.",
      "a": "as",
      "b": "since",
      "c": "for",
      "d": "because",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- For: used to introduce the reason for something [= because]",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ the president's speech was a long one, nobody lost interest.",
      "a": "Because",
      "b": "As",
      "c": "Though",
      "d": "Even",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Though: used to introduce a statement that makes the main statement coming after it seem surprising, unlikely, or unexpected",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The suspicious mother thought I was talking about her daughter, ___, in fact, I was talking about mine.",
      "a": "where",
      "b": "whom",
      "c": "while",
      "d": "which",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- While: used to emphasize the difference between two situations, activities",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ we'll go mountain climbing tomorrow depends on the weather.",
      "a": "Whether",
      "b": "If",
      "c": "Where",
      "d": "That",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Whether: used when talking about a choice you have to make or about something that is not certain",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The reason for his absence is ___ he was out on business.",
      "a": "why",
      "b": "that",
      "c": "for",
      "d": "because",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n-That: used after verbs, nouns, and adjectives to introduce a clause which shows what someone says or thinks, or states a fact or reason",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Speak slowly ___ everybody can follow what you're saying.",
      "a": "so that",
      "b": "since",
      "c": "because",
      "d": "for",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- So that: in order to make something happen, make something possible",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}